contextualpsychology.org 2007-12-12

# Privacy Policy | Association for Contextual Behavioral Science

Protecting your privacy is important to us. Because we gather certain types of information from visitors and registered users of our site, we feel you should be fully aware of the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

**Why we collect personal information**  
ContextualPsychology.org uses any information voluntarily provided by our users to promote an open scientific community and to encourage the contribution and sharing of relevant knowledge, content, and resources. This information is not used for any commercial purposes. ContextualPsychology.org also tracks user traffic patterns through our site. For visitors, this data is not correlated with individual users. For registered users of the site, this data (including number of site contributions and comments posted, as reported in the "Hall of Fame") may be correlated with individual users.

**How we collect personal information**  
We collect information about you in several ways. Certain information, such as the type of browser, computer, and operating system you are using, is automatically collected by your web browser. Additional information is collected when users register for the site. The website also uses “cookies” technology to collect and store certain information (see below).

**Cookies**  
We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain personal information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. We use cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above) and to allow registered users the option of being automatically "logged in" to the website on future visits. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site.

**When we disclose personal information**  
Your username and any additional information you voluntarily provide about yourself during the registration process will be publicly available to all registered users of the site on the Member List page. Your email address will not be publicly available, but you will have the option to allow visitors and users of the site to contact you via a web-based form that does not reveal your email address. Your email address or other personal information will never be sold or released to any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors, or partners. The Association for Contextual Behavioral Science (ACBS), the owner of this site, will not use your personal information for any commercial purposes. At times we may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we believe that disclosure is necessary for the public interest.

**Access to your personal information**  
You always have access to the information we have about you. To review and update your personal contact information at any time, simply click on the "my account" link on the left side of the screen.
